[{"answer": "2016.", "docId": "120910pmt", "aSentId": 27, "question": "What year?", "qSentId": 26}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120910pmt", "aSentId": 92, "question": "That was lower?", "qSentId": 91}, {"answer": "I'll tell you, if you give me equal man and woman, the difference is, if you watch a Saturday morning TV commercial, a woman -- a girl -- it's always four girls playing together, it's always one boy go, I won.", "docId": "120910pmt", "aSentId": 160, "question": "Isn't it obvious?", "qSentId": 159}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120910pmt", "aSentId": 165, "question": "But Suze, have you seen that women are much more reticent to ask for a raise than men?", "qSentId": 164}, {"answer": "We're the fixers.", "docId": "120910pmt", "aSentId": 171, "question": "Men, are you kidding?", "qSentId": 170}, {"answer": "I don't think they decide it, but I think it can help them, it can enhance.", "docId": "120910pmt", "aSentId": 207, "question": "Is this dumb guy talking?", "qSentId": 206}, {"answer": "Utility shows like \"The Doctors,\" should take home, shows like what Suze does where people could take something away.", "docId": "120910pmt", "aSentId": 247, "question": "What do you -- when you say utility, what do you mean?", "qSentId": 246}, {"answer": "I think there's always room for something good.", "docId": "120910pmt", "aSentId": 251, "question": "Is that a relevant subject matter anymore?", "qSentId": 250}, {"answer": "No, I know exactly --", "docId": "120910pmt", "aSentId": 255, "question": "You know where I'm going with this?", "qSentId": 254}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120910pmt", "aSentId": 277, "question": "One guy and four women, something like that?", "qSentId": 276}, {"answer": "You're an ABC person.", "docId": "120910pmt", "aSentId": 294, "question": "I think she could be a huge -- look at what she did?", "qSentId": 293}, {"answer": "I'm happy to take them off.", "docId": "120910pmt", "aSentId": 331, "question": "You're going to the airport today, I say you don't have to take off your shoes, you go (INAUDIBLE)?", "qSentId": 330}, {"answer": "I actual did for research.", "docId": "120910pmt", "aSentId": 399, "question": "So here's the real question, how many women on this panel read that book?", "qSentId": 398}, {"answer": "Of course I did.", "docId": "120910pmt", "aSentId": 405, "question": "You do read it?", "qSentId": 404}, {"answer": "I know what it's about.", "docId": "120910pmt", "aSentId": 414, "question": "But Serena, do you know what it's about?", "qSentId": 413}, {"answer": "I know the basic premise.", "docId": "120910pmt", "aSentId": 419, "question": "Did you read it?", "qSentId": 418}, {"answer": "No, absolutely not.", "docId": "120910pmt", "aSentId": 428, "question": "Donny -- are you a spanker?", "qSentId": 427}, {"answer": "I think it is.", "docId": "120910pmt", "aSentId": 466, "question": "Is that intimidating to a lot of men?", "qSentId": 465}, {"answer": "If you and I --", "docId": "120910pmt", "aSentId": 470, "question": "Are you intimidated by me, Donny?", "qSentId": 469}, {"answer": "Yes, I do.", "docId": "120910pmt", "aSentId": 475, "question": "You're gorgeous, so I'm curious, do you run into that?", "qSentId": 474}, {"answer": "That's 59 years the way they care for each other.", "docId": "120910pmt", "aSentId": 566, "question": "How many years?", "qSentId": 565}, {"answer": "It's difficult but for me, I'm just normal individual.", "docId": "120910pmt", "aSentId": 588, "question": "How do you live normal?", "qSentId": 587}, {"answer": "They're the royals.", "docId": "120910pmt", "aSentId": 602, "question": "Why do we care?", "qSentId": 601}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120910pmt", "aSentId": 630, "question": "Does that mean Serena, as a tennis star, does she have an obligation to young people to act a certain way?", "qSentId": 629}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120910pmt", "aSentId": 662, "question": "Does Piers know we're here?", "qSentId": 661}, {"answer": "Divorce is very painful.", "docId": "120910pmt", "aSentId": 679, "question": "What is it?", "qSentId": 678}, {"answer": "I did, I did.", "docId": "120910pmt", "aSentId": 743, "question": "Did you ever doubt yourself yesterday?", "qSentId": 742}, {"answer": "Believe it or not, very much the same is that an Orman never -- my mother always taught me that an Orman nerve gives up.", "docId": "120910pmt", "aSentId": 758, "question": "What was the turning point for you?", "qSentId": 757}, {"answer": "The common thing you both said it is came from your parents.", "docId": "120910pmt", "aSentId": 778, "question": "Where does this come from?", "qSentId": 777}, {"answer": "That's easy.", "docId": "120910pmt", "aSentId": 782, "question": "When we come back, I'm going to ask each one of you what year will be our first female president?", "qSentId": 781}, {"answer": "2016.", "docId": "120910pmt", "aSentId": 794, "question": "What year?", "qSentId": 793}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120910pmt", "aSentId": 798, "question": "Is that a Hillary?", "qSentId": 797}, {"answer": "I hope never.", "docId": "120910pmt", "aSentId": 809, "question": "Lara?", "qSentId": 808}, {"answer": "I think he did what he set out to do.", "docId": "120910pmt", "aSentId": 820, "question": "Lara?", "qSentId": 819}, {"answer": "I think for the party he should have stayed home, because I don't think it really helped in the long run.", "docId": "120910pmt", "aSentId": 831, "question": "Should he have stayed home?", "qSentId": 830}, {"answer": "No, no.", "docId": "120910pmt", "aSentId": 836, "question": "Do you guys think it damaged his brand at all?", "qSentId": 835}, {"answer": "That's awesome.", "docId": "120910pmt", "aSentId": 851, "question": "I think he was in a pizza place?", "qSentId": 850}, {"answer": "No, I don't think so.", "docId": "120910pmt", "aSentId": 855, "question": "Let's start with you, Serena?", "qSentId": 854}, {"answer": "No, I'm just saying, when you see him at baseball games -- no, no, of course that was not staged.", "docId": "120910pmt", "aSentId": 868, "question": "Do you think that was staged?", "qSentId": 867}, {"answer": "God, I have no idea what he would do there or in any situation, for that matter.", "docId": "120910pmt", "aSentId": 870, "question": "The question was, what would Mitt have done in that situation?", "qSentId": 869}, {"answer": "OK, more lightning round, Suze.", "docId": "120910pmt", "aSentId": 918, "question": "Are you kidding me?", "qSentId": 917}, {"answer": "Well, if you didn't know -- just on the surface, because this is -- who knows them, really.", "docId": "120910pmt", "aSentId": 934, "question": "Suze?", "qSentId": 933}, {"answer": "I think each of the -- I'm going to give a politically correct answer, because I do know Kim and I think she's a great girl.", "docId": "120910pmt", "aSentId": 959, "question": "Serena?", "qSentId": 958}]